

Contact

Bhawal Jamalpur, Kaliganj, Gazipur +8801316447745 (Work) m0takabbir@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/motakabbir (LinkedIn) motakabbir.com (Personal) techsmsbd.com (Blog)

Top Skills

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Linux

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
Korean (Limited Working)
Hindi (Limited Working)

Certifications

Learning Graphic Design: Layouts
Learning Catalog Design
Graphic Design Masterclass - Learn
GREAT Design by Lindsay Marsh
First Step Korean
Graphic Design

Motakabbir Hossan

Freelance Graphic Designer Gazipur District

Summary

I am an Engineering Student. I started Graphic design 4 years ago now it became my passion.

I love to work with pixels. I have 3+ years of Graphic Design skills. I am very proficient at Photoshop and

Illustrator. My Linkedin Profile also says that. This proficiency is built by the amount of time I invested in this sector.

I do Print-Design, Marketing & Advertising, Package & Product Design, Signage Design, Image Retouching, and also all kinds of Photo treatment.

I also have HTML, CSS knowledge with WordPress and JavaScript. I believe these skills drove me to the right path that I have chosen.

Experience

Glorious Bangladesh Creative Content Creator August 2021 - Present (2 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

Fiverr

Freelance Graphic Designer
April 2016 - Present (5 years 6 months)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Upwork
Graphic Designer
March 2015 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Freelancer.com
Freelance Graphic Designer
April 2016 - Present (5 years 6 months)
Dhaka, Bangladesh

techSMSBD

Co-Founder Co-Administrator and Content Creator November 2015 - Present (5 years 11 months)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Education

Shyamoli Textile Engineering College

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (January 2020 - August 2024)

National Ideal School & College

Higher Secondary School Certificate, Science · (June 2017 - July 2019)

Janata Adarsha Bidyapith

ssc, Student Counseling and Personnel Services · (2006 - 2017)